<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="hello">Hello World, MainMenu!</string>
	<string name="app_name">NotifyMyWay</string>
	<string name="edit_preferences">Edit Preferences</string>
	<string name="edit_pattern_dialog_name">Pattern Name:</string>
	<string name="edit_pattern_dialog_pattern">Pattern: (See Help)</string>
	<string name="save_pattern_button">Save</string>
	<string name="cancel_pattern_button">Cancel</string>
	<drawable name="vp_list_item_pattern_color">#A1A1A1</drawable>
	<string name="welcome_text">Welcome to NotifyMyWay.\n
		\nNotifyMyWay allows you
		to change how you\'re notified when you receive a Text Message (SMS).
	</string>
	<string name="help_button">Help</string>
	<string name="help_back_button">Back</string>
	<string name="help_activity_text">
		Thank you for installing NotifyMyWay.
		\n\n
		<b>Introduction</b>
		\nNotifyMyWay allows you to change how your phone vibrates when
		receiving text messages.
		\n\n
		<b>Eliminate Vibration Overlap</b>
		\nTo use NotifyMyWay fully, you will need to deactivate vibration in
		your current text messaging (SMS) application. In the standard Android
		application you can find this setting at Menu->Messaging
		Settings->Text messaging settings->Vibrate.
		\n\n
		<b>Choosing Your Vibration Pattern</b>
		\nSelect \"Edit Preferences\" in the main menu. From here you may
		toggle vibration, select and edit Vibration Patterns, and test your
		current vibration pattern.

		\n\nPress \"Select Vibration Pattern...\".
		This takes you to the Vibration Pattern Manager. Click on a Vibration
		Pattern to select it or press and hold to edit it. To add a new
		Vibration Pattern press \"Add Pattern\" in the bottom left (see
		\"Custom Vibration Patterns\" below). Press \"Cancel\" to return
		without changing anything. \n\nOnce you have selected a Vibration
		Pattern by pressing or clicking it, you will return to the preferences
		menu and your new pattern will be tested for you.
		\n\n
		<b>Custom Vibration Patterns</b>
		\nIf you can\'t quite grasp this section, it\'s okay. Just use the
		built in patterns. An easy to use Vibration Pattern editor is being
		developed and will come in a future update.
		\n\n
		Here\'s Google\'s
		explanation: \n \"...The [Vibration Pattern] defines the alternating
		pattern for the length of vibration off and on (in milliseconds). The
		first value is how long to wait (off) before beginning, the second
		value is the length of the first vibration, the third is the next
		length off, and so on...\"\n\n Vibration patterns are a comma
		separated group of number time lengths. The numbers are Milliseconds
		(1,000 milliseconds = 1 second). So a pattern that goes immediately
		on,
		vibrates for a half second, waits a half second, and then vibrates
		for a second would be \"0,500,500,1000\".
	</string>
</resources>
